export const intPrepPlace =[
     {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "There are a lot of people swimming _________ the river today.",
        "options": [
            "next to",
            "under",
            "in",
            "on"
        ],
        "answer": "in"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Do you see that dirty mark _________ the ceiling?",
        "options": [
            "under",
            "in",
            "in front of",
            "on"
        ],
        "answer": "on"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Who is that man standing _________ the bus stop?.",
        "options": [
            "under",
            "at",
            "on",
            "behind"
        ],
        "answer": "at"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "I'll met you _________ the hotel lobby at 7pm.",
        "options": [
            "under",
            "on",
            "in",
            "through"
        ],
        "answer": "in"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "There's someone knocking _________ the front door.",
        "options": [
            "in front of",
            "in",
            "at",
            "under"
        ],
        "answer": "at"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "The angry landlord pinned an eviction notice _________ the door.",
        "options": [
            "in",
            "on",
            "under",
            "in front of"
        ],
        "answer": "on"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "There are suspicious meetings going on _________ closed doors these days.",
        "options": [
            "in",
            "under",
            "behind",
            "next to"
        ],
        "answer": "behind"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "I hope I can retire _________ an island one day.",
        "options": [
            "on",
            "in",
            "under",
            "in front of"
        ],
        "answer": "on"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "The pimple _________ my nose hurts so much!",
        "options": [
            "next to",
            "in front of",
            "above",
            "on"
        ],
        "answer": "on"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "The police escort came first. The president was in the car _________ it.",
        "options": [
            "on",
            "under",
            "behind",
            "next to"
        ],
        "answer": "behind"
    }
]